<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Brockmans]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Brockmans]]></description>
        <link>http://brockmans.org/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:23:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://brockmans.org/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:23:37 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A taste of Renovaré]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>A taste of Renovaré</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>My start date for <a href="https://renovare.org/institute/overview" title="Renovaré Institute">Renovaré Institute for Spiritual Formation</a> was August 1st. Each month we are answering a theological question as well as meditating on a particular passage from the Bible. We are in a learning environment which values the importance of possessing good theology while knowing that it requires encountering God to change us. Thus, the curriculum has those two streams, solid theological learning with opportunities to encounter the biblical Jesus.</p>,<p>Who is God?</p>,<p>What is the Gospel?</p>,<p>Who are we?</p>,<p>Last week, the 40 other students in my cohort and I filled <a href="http://La Casa de Maria retreat center/" title="La Casa de Maria">La Casa de Maria retreat center</a> in Santa Barbara, California for our first of four residential weeks of learning with our instructors. I struggle to find words to capture that week. To capture the richness of the teaching, our instructors, as well as the relationships formed on paper isn’t possible. Yet I want to offer you a taste.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/31c64f17-2fee-439a-ae8e-1c4500d4f95c.jpg" title="Living quarters">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6d9a7936-0407-4c94-80e3-18f9ab177faf.jpg">,<p>As I was en route back to Orlando after a life-changing week, I texted Dennis something like this to capture one reality resonating in me from the week:</p>,<p>“I was introduced to such a gentle vision of the gospel.”</p>,<p>God is a lover ever-pouring Himself into us if we allow, never forcing Himself upon us, yet continually wooing us into His Kingdom. In the <a href="https://smile.amazon.com/gp/product/0060693339/ref=s9u_simh_gw_i1?ie=UTF8&amp;fpl=fresh&amp;pd_rd_i=0060693339&amp;pd_rd_r=c8954873-bbe9-11e7-8cdf-51a46fae6b0a&amp;pd_rd_w=ejVas&amp;pd_rd_wg=utrbt&amp;pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&amp;pf_rd_s=&amp;pf_rd_r=XY9RFZTRQTF09DCK3V74&amp;pf_rd_t=36701&amp;pf_rd_p=1cf9d009-399c-49e1-901a-7b8786e59436&amp;pf_rd_i=desktop" title="Divine Conspiracy at Amazon">Divine Conspiracy</a>, Dallas Willard captures a taste of God’s essence in this statement,</p>,<p>“But he is simply one great inexhaustible and eternal experience of all that is good and true and beautiful and right. This is what we must think of when we hear theologians and philosophers speak of him as a perfect being. This is his life.”</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/05487dff-bb81-402d-a590-c1f74d008893.jpg" title="One of the many prayer gardens on site">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/dfb881d2-b78a-415f-9adf-02acd30a32b4.jpg" title="A labyrinth for meditative prayer walking">,<p>Throughout my coursework thus far, my vision of God is expanding, I am tasting His goodness more richly, and feeling His heartbeat for me more palpably. My understanding of the Gospel has expanded beyond it’s small borders to something far more expansive than I’d ever imagined.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d2d06dfb-21eb-4f42-ae37-09503621fdae.jpg" title="My fabulous small group">,<p>Finally, being surrounded by a learning community of people with a shared desire to know God, love Him well, live well, and pour His love into others was the richest of fare. For those of you who have given so that I may so richly receive, know that you were there with me in thought throughout the week. Gratitude for you is bursting forth.</p>,<p>PS. I’ll elaborate on the above topics and in more detail in future posts.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/a-taste-of-renovare/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0b92c0d-c6e2-4f38-9b4a-061125b44907</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 12:21:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making Digital Disciples]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Making Digital Disciples</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/07d1d0c4-6969-4254-a0a8-918ad6d2838a.jpg">,<p>Some call them Millennials. Others the I-Gen. Born between 1982 – 2004. Here’s one description of them...</p>,<blockquote>Millennials, and the generations that follow, &ZeroWidthSpace;are shaping technology. This generation has grown up with computing in the palm of their hands. They are more socially and globally connected through mobile Internet devices than any prior generation. And they don&apos;t question; they just learn.Brad D. Smith (CEO Intuit)</blockquote>,<p>Many Millennials are technically-gifted and enmeshed in a world of computer languages like Python, Swift, HTML5, Java, etc. They are responsible for our devices serving us terabytes of entertainment, news, remote control services, home automation, and more. Many of them follow Jesus, and would love to use their interests and skills to reach others for Jesus Christ.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5e4648ef-7f58-46b5-a0ce-c9cf7dbbc46e.png">,<p>We have a ministry designed to engage followers of Christ and future Christians called <a href="https://indigitous.org/">Indigitous</a>. <a href="https://indigitous.org/">Indigitous</a> is a global community engaging with ideas and each other to advance God’s Kingdom through technical innovation.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/eaa1bb26-06b1-489f-8b5a-37d9a08d7642.jpg">,<p>One Indigitous strategy is to host hackathons. From October 20-22, we will have the privilege of hosting our second <a href="https://indigitous.org/hack/">Global Missional Hackathon called Indigitous #HACK!</a> 2500+ missional hackers are gathering in 38+ cities around the world, developing digital disciplers who will work on missional projects.</p>,<p>Through your support of Lisa and me, you are helping to launch thousands of digital disciples whose heart is to help fulfill the Great Commission using their tech-genius skills.</p>,<p>P.S. If you know someone that could, would, should come to the #HACK, let them know about it. Send them the poster above and or send them this url <a href="https://indigitous.org/hack/">https://indigitous.org/hack/</a>.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/making-digital-disciples/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3b6af503-6ce5-448d-9396-6fc066a67a51</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 20:50:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are we growing? These numbers say, “Yes!”!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Are we growing? These numbers say, “Yes!”!</h1>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FXA4VtIVem6k%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DXA4VtIVem6k&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FXA4VtIVem6k%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>Jesse is a creative artist with Cru. It was nine years ago we hosted our 1st Creative Artists Guild of Cru staff. We met in Hilton Head where nearly 25 us got to know each other for the first time, shared best practices and worked through professional skill training to develop our crafts in telling God's stories. Since then we hosted five gatherings in Orlando, and I met Jesse for the first time in one of those.</p>,<p>Jesse just posted in our guild G+ forum a video he worked on this past summer for our national staff conference. It did not show (sometimes this is the hard life of a creative), but I will show it to you. It may not have fit the program this summer, but the numbers it displays represent people and the work of God's Spirit. If you have just under 2 minutes, it presents encouraging ground taken for God's glorious Kingdom.</p>,<p>I share this because you and I are part of these people and these happenings and it is pleasurable to peek at one part of what God is doing in and through us.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUEOwiAQQNGrkDlA0Wi7MKXGpRdo3BaYChGKGYZMvL2NLv_m_TGutGRUEj0HA_1wABUwPgMbOB17UJWcgcD8rhetRaT7lMbNYudK1pgtev24nWe-z5iH15UwmZ34obaQRzKw95JSkbWlVB0hbtOo_9_pC7peK5s</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">34735f4f-7cfb-4a34-8cc5-54c82e060583</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 16:23:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are we growing? These numbers say, “Yes!”!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Are we growing? These numbers say, “Yes!”!</h1>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FXA4VtIVem6k%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DXA4VtIVem6k&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FXA4VtIVem6k%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>Jesse is a creative artist with Cru. It was nine years ago we hosted our 1st Creative Artists Guild of Cru staff. We met in Hilton Head where nearly 25 us got to know each other for the first time, shared best practices and worked through professional skill training to develop our crafts in telling God's stories. Since then we hosted five gatherings in Orlando, and I met Jesse for the first time in one of those.</p>,<p>Jesse just posted in our guild G+ forum a video he worked on this past summer for our national staff conference. It did not show (sometimes this is the hard life of a creative), but I will show it to you. It may not have fit the program this summer, but the numbers it displays represent people and the work of God's Spirit. If you have just under 2 minutes, it presents encouraging ground taken for God's glorious Kingdom.</p>,<p>I share this because you and I are part of these people and these happenings and it is pleasurable to peek at one part of what God is doing in and through us.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUEOwiAQQNGrkDlA0Wi7MKXGpRdo3BaYChGKGYZMvL2NLv_m_TGutGRUEj0HA_1wABUwPgMbOB17UJWcgcD8rhetRaT7lMbNYudK1pgtev24nWe-z5iH15UwmZ34obaQRzKw95JSkbWlVB0hbtOo_9_pC7peK5s</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d1ab1c-98ae-4f51-a228-4876552ed6fd</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 18:55:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Survived Irma]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>We Survived Irma</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>Because some of you are asking, we are sending a little update from O-town. We fared well through the storm. The climax of Irma began around six last night and continued through the evening with continuous tornado warnings, one of which passed right over us. These created some tension within us. The wind howled, belting trees in every direction and rain pummeled the earth as we drifted to sleep, hoping and praying for protection from these forces of nature. We awoke to light winds and sun peeking through this morning. Thankfully, we fared well as did our neighborhood. Some trees and fences are down. There are roof shingles here and there, but the damage is mild given the destruction others have experienced from Irma. Here are some photos from around our house.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/257da3d9-474e-4204-aa56-503fffb135dd.jpg">,<p>Downed trees were a common sight around our neighborhood. This picture is our backyard.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d93a444f-0fde-4489-9ae4-feea62ae7717.jpg">,<h2>Irma left everything messy</h2>,<p>Once cleanup from Irma began, our streets were lined with piles of branches from trees.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3406f3ca-eb63-4d64-86be-9998224b1105.jpg">,<h3>Rebuild and Replant</h3>,<p>Our neighbor had two trees down. Others had fences go down.</p>,<h3>Cabin Fever</h3>,<p>Out of a case of cabin fever, Brockman studios produced a few videos.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUEKwjAQAMCvhH1AV5H2IE1BxIPgrd6lSbYmkDSySVj8vaIfmBnDyksiJcFVr6EfdqA8haevGg77HlRhq8HX-ipHRBHp3rnVZqizOSElQw5PV_Mw9ny7zxdQP85kdsQavtgSY5a1xVgsE23TiP9x-gC89SmO" height="244"></iframe>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJyzKbDj4rLRL7ADAApgAhg" height="244"></iframe>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUEOwiAQAMCvkH1AV2PwYEoPXjwYLyY-oMBWSEAaWLL19xr9wMwYlzpnUhI9BwP6uAMVKD4DGzjsNahWnYHAvLYToogM79K5WxpcyUjZkke9XS_2Hh_b-Qbqx9lSPVUDX2xOqcjSU2quEr2mEf_j9AHFFSm7" height="244"></iframe>,<h3>We give thanks</h3>,<p>We are grateful for your prayers and that God is a protector. Had the damage been worse, He would still be our protector. We were incredibly blessed never to have lost power. Sooooooooo thankful for this! We have friends whose yards and streets are flooded and are without power. Our neighborhood seems to shine in its drainage abilities. Whew.</p>,<p>As Keegs and Dennis walked around the neighborhood this morning to survey the damage, a police officer told them Orlando is under a curfew until 6 pm and to go home. Glad there’s only one day more we are under a curfew, and we enjoy so much freedom in America.</p>,<p>Thank you again, for your thoughts and prayers. Our Father generously answered.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/because-some-of-you-are-asking-we-are-sending-a-little-upda/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a2189c1b-40c3-494d-802b-515b363324f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 19:07:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What it feels like]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/50d06329b8d5d6be46a308c7c94c6b26/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=498&cropwidth=400&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F2d80910c-2e06-482e-9b97-be2549c19b49.jpg&x=0&y=1">,<h1><strong>What it feels like</strong></h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>The <a href="https://youtu.be/BX3bN5YeiQs">music score</a> brought on an intensity that moved you to the edge of your seat. Caught between horror and fear, you tensed for the next victim. If I played the unmistakable tune, you’d likely know it instantly--the 1975 thriller, Jaws.</p>,<p>Awaiting Hurricane Irma feels a bit like that. The havoc Harvey inflicted upon Houston ramps up the intensity for Irma. Tweets, web headlines, and chatter about the storm has a similar impact to the music score in Jaws.</p>,<h3>Madison</h3>,<p>Palm Beach Atlantic University closed after class yesterday and won’t re-open until Tuesday. This released Madison to drive home last night, surrounded by multitudes of South Floridians evacuating in preparation for Irma. She was in the thick of bumper-to-bumper traffic all the way home to Orlando, adding an hour to her usual three-hour commute.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/db6f6c16-903f-4e7a-889a-466afeb8d5bd.png">,<p>Note the red indicating heavy traffic (or slow traffic)</p>,<h3>Keegan</h3>,<p>Our Gator (UF mascot), Keegan, is at school in Gainesville. UF is canceling classes on Monday, the day after Irma is to strike our area. Keegan plans to stay in Gainesville, study, and ride out the storm with whoever remains.</p>,<h3>Us</h3>,<p>We intend to ride out Irma at home. We considered leaving the area, but our schools here in Orlando are in session until Friday, and we’re hoping as Irma moves across land, she’ll slow a bit as she reaches central Florida.</p>,<h3>Our meteorology report</h3>,<p>We are 45 miles inland from the coast. The hurricane force winds are currently measuring 50 miles from the eye. If the eye runs up the coast, we will be on the outer edge of the high winds.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b004454b-119f-4535-9363-a188f6102e25.png">,<p>This is what they project will be the path of Irma</p>,<p>We are preparing as best as we are able. It’s wild walking aisles of the grocery store with shelves completely emptied. It’s actually a bit eerie. Our hearts are so burdened for the islands being pummeled by Irma right now. We’d love your prayers for us as well as for all those in Irma’s path and wake. We will send an update as soon as we are able after the storm.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/what-it-feels-like/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">524ebd82-03fe-45fc-af9a-be368739d76d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 18:25:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transition]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e8b0f89a-35b5-45fa-8af7-f32a96054767.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9dd6b956-7eb5-4495-9f31-98132eeb088a.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6a850a26-e9a5-4296-9944-66e75b8acbb2.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bd6a912a-7358-414e-a812-d267c848ffac.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/faee6ad4-9f07-406d-a4fc-456e59194249.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/38b288c1-b945-4649-8dbd-d6bbba9c82c5.jpg">,<h1>Transition</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>It was through Storytelling that Jesus penetrated souls. It was through storytelling that he turned the world of the Pharisees upside down. It was through His story that the world has been revolutionized. Throughout the past 15 years, I have been given the pleasure of influencing Cru's storytelling through visual communication. For the past three years, you and I have been storytellers for Global Fund Development.</p>,<p>Today, I will step into a new role as Cru's Global Marketing and Experience director. Since Cru began a re-branding journey six years ago, I've had a fire burning within me to see Cru's messaging internally and externally streamlined with such precision that our storytelling will have even greater impact. Lisa, Madison (as a writer) and three other people I've loved working with over the years will join me on the Global Digital Strategies team. We are blessed to work under and support our Vice President, Ken Cochrum, who leads the Digital Strategies team.</p>,<p>Together, God-willing, we will do this so that we can even more effectively tell the gospel story <em>so that everyone knows someone who follows Jesus Christ.</em></p>,<p>You are so critical in our being able to do this work.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/transition/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ae74ea1-47b0-46b7-8e04-a262dece0eaa</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 21:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Something about us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/836cf4ab-99f0-47ee-9923-2839037f6c97.jpg">,<h1>Something about us</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>We are so glad you clicked on over. Here’s a small window into who we are...</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJyzyShSKM6sSrVVMjRQsgMAIgYEEg" height="10"></iframe>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/81b1bd93-f190-4d63-8f00-38079fbc7f41.jpg" title="A note from Lisa">,<h2>I bit about Lisa</h2>,<p>I am a mom to five mostly fabulous kids ranging from 13-21 years of age. For 13 of my 21 years of parenting, I was privileged to home educate our kids, some hours with much joy and delight...others through gnashing of teeth. We bathed together in the deep waters of spiritual formation. I think especially me. That was fertile ground for the passion God has deposited within me for spiritual formation.</p>,<p>I’m most alive when I’m journeying with others on their road of personal transformation as well as when others join me in mine. Thirteen years ago, I participated in my first School of Spiritual Direction through Larry Crabb’s <a href="http://www.newwayministries.org/" title="New Way Ministries">New Way Ministries</a> as a personal development pursuit. That week rocked my world in the best way. I caught a vision of God, myself, and others I’d never seen before, and a passion grew within me to share this vision and walk alongside others in their spiritual journeys. I acquired my Spiritual Direction certificate in the summer of 2016, and find incredible joy in journeying with Cru staff into the heart of God.</p>,<p>The summer of 2017 marked my 25-year anniversary as a Cru staff member. I currently serve with the Digital Strategies team in the area of Spiritual Formation.</p>,<p>I am in a graduate studies two-year program I began in August 2017 called <a href="https://renovare.org/institute/overview" title="Renovare Institute">Renovare Institute for Spiritual Formation</a>.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJyzyShSKM6sSrVVMjRQsgMAIgYEEg" height="10"></iframe>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7663b16b-202c-4364-a167-e780698622f9.jpg" title="A note from Dennis">,<h2>A bit about Dennis</h2>,<p>I am a dad to five lively kids who keep me active on athletic sidelines, and are wonderful objects of interest for my photography hobby. Parenting them is a gift and as they grow into young adulthood, relating with them grows even richer.</p>,<p>The summer of 2018 marks my 35-year anniversary as a Cru staff member. I am passionate about the spiritual life and co-journeying with others who share the desire to know God intimately. I’m also passionate about how Christ is presented to the world, for how He’s presented often determines whether or not one opens the door to listen to the transforming message of Christ. It is my privilege to serve on our Global Digital Strategy team on which I focus on marketing our Cru message and give attentiveness to how we are experienced as messengers.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJyzyShSKM6sSrVVMjRQsgMAIgYEEg" height="10"></iframe>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6ee7cdf4-9d70-4d04-94ae-e8c457859941.jpg">,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/something-about-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">efb2f6c6-1243-447f-b59e-1fceca264511</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 18:41:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>