<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Brockmans]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Brockmans]]></description>
        <link>http://brockmans.org/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 21:18:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://brockmans.org/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 21:18:57 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Survived Irma]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>We Survived Irma</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>Because some of you are asking, we are sending a little update from O-town. We fared well through the storm. The climax of Irma began around six last night and continued through the evening with continuous tornado warnings, one of which passed right over us. These created some tension within us. The wind howled, belting trees in every direction and rain pummeled the earth as we drifted to sleep, hoping and praying for protection from these forces of nature. We awoke to light winds and sun peeking through this morning. Thankfully, we fared well as did our neighborhood. Some trees and fences are down. There are roof shingles here and there, but the damage is mild given the destruction others have experienced from Irma. Here are some photos from around our house.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/257da3d9-474e-4204-aa56-503fffb135dd.jpg">,<p>Downed trees were a common sight around our neighborhood. This picture is our backyard.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d93a444f-0fde-4489-9ae4-feea62ae7717.jpg">,<h2>Irma left everything messy</h2>,<p>Once cleanup from Irma began, our streets were lined with piles of branches from trees.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3406f3ca-eb63-4d64-86be-9998224b1105.jpg">,<h3>Rebuild and Replant</h3>,<p>Our neighbor had two trees down. Others had fences go down.</p>,<h3>Cabin Fever</h3>,<p>Out of a case of cabin fever, Brockman studios produced a few videos.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUEKwjAQAMCvhH1AV5H2IE1BxIPgrd6lSbYmkDSySVj8vaIfmBnDyksiJcFVr6EfdqA8haevGg77HlRhq8HX-ipHRBHp3rnVZqizOSElQw5PV_Mw9ny7zxdQP85kdsQavtgSY5a1xVgsE23TiP9x-gC89SmO" height="244"></iframe>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJyzKbDj4rLRL7ADAApgAhg" height="244"></iframe>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUEOwiAQAMCvkH1AV2PwYEoPXjwYLyY-oMBWSEAaWLL19xr9wMwYlzpnUhI9BwP6uAMVKD4DGzjsNahWnYHAvLYToogM79K5WxpcyUjZkke9XS_2Hh_b-Qbqx9lSPVUDX2xOqcjSU2quEr2mEf_j9AHFFSm7" height="244"></iframe>,<h3>We give thanks</h3>,<p>We are grateful for your prayers and that God is a protector. Had the damage been worse, He would still be our protector. We were incredibly blessed never to have lost power. Sooooooooo thankful for this! We have friends whose yards and streets are flooded and are without power. Our neighborhood seems to shine in its drainage abilities. Whew.</p>,<p>As Keegs and Dennis walked around the neighborhood this morning to survey the damage, a police officer told them Orlando is under a curfew until 6 pm and to go home. Glad there’s only one day more we are under a curfew, and we enjoy so much freedom in America.</p>,<p>Thank you again, for your thoughts and prayers. Our Father generously answered.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/because-some-of-you-are-asking-we-are-sending-a-little-upda/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a2189c1b-40c3-494d-802b-515b363324f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 19:07:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What it feels like]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/50d06329b8d5d6be46a308c7c94c6b26/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=498&cropwidth=400&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F2d80910c-2e06-482e-9b97-be2549c19b49.jpg&x=0&y=1">,<h1><strong>What it feels like</strong></h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>The <a href="https://youtu.be/BX3bN5YeiQs">music score</a> brought on an intensity that moved you to the edge of your seat. Caught between horror and fear, you tensed for the next victim. If I played the unmistakable tune, you’d likely know it instantly--the 1975 thriller, Jaws.</p>,<p>Awaiting Hurricane Irma feels a bit like that. The havoc Harvey inflicted upon Houston ramps up the intensity for Irma. Tweets, web headlines, and chatter about the storm has a similar impact to the music score in Jaws.</p>,<h3>Madison</h3>,<p>Palm Beach Atlantic University closed after class yesterday and won’t re-open until Tuesday. This released Madison to drive home last night, surrounded by multitudes of South Floridians evacuating in preparation for Irma. She was in the thick of bumper-to-bumper traffic all the way home to Orlando, adding an hour to her usual three-hour commute.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/db6f6c16-903f-4e7a-889a-466afeb8d5bd.png">,<p>Note the red indicating heavy traffic (or slow traffic)</p>,<h3>Keegan</h3>,<p>Our Gator (UF mascot), Keegan, is at school in Gainesville. UF is canceling classes on Monday, the day after Irma is to strike our area. Keegan plans to stay in Gainesville, study, and ride out the storm with whoever remains.</p>,<h3>Us</h3>,<p>We intend to ride out Irma at home. We considered leaving the area, but our schools here in Orlando are in session until Friday, and we’re hoping as Irma moves across land, she’ll slow a bit as she reaches central Florida.</p>,<h3>Our meteorology report</h3>,<p>We are 45 miles inland from the coast. The hurricane force winds are currently measuring 50 miles from the eye. If the eye runs up the coast, we will be on the outer edge of the high winds.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b004454b-119f-4535-9363-a188f6102e25.png">,<p>This is what they project will be the path of Irma</p>,<p>We are preparing as best as we are able. It’s wild walking aisles of the grocery store with shelves completely emptied. It’s actually a bit eerie. Our hearts are so burdened for the islands being pummeled by Irma right now. We’d love your prayers for us as well as for all those in Irma’s path and wake. We will send an update as soon as we are able after the storm.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/what-it-feels-like/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">524ebd82-03fe-45fc-af9a-be368739d76d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 18:25:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transition]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e8b0f89a-35b5-45fa-8af7-f32a96054767.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9dd6b956-7eb5-4495-9f31-98132eeb088a.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6a850a26-e9a5-4296-9944-66e75b8acbb2.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bd6a912a-7358-414e-a812-d267c848ffac.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/faee6ad4-9f07-406d-a4fc-456e59194249.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/38b288c1-b945-4649-8dbd-d6bbba9c82c5.jpg">,<h1>Transition</h1>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>,<p>It was through Storytelling that Jesus penetrated souls. It was through storytelling that he turned the world of the Pharisees upside down. It was through His story that the world has been revolutionized. Throughout the past 15 years, I have been given the pleasure of influencing Cru's storytelling through visual communication. For the past three years, you and I have been storytellers for Global Fund Development.</p>,<p>Today, I will step into a new role as Cru's Global Marketing and Experience director. Since Cru began a re-branding journey six years ago, I've had a fire burning within me to see Cru's messaging internally and externally streamlined with such precision that our storytelling will have even greater impact. Lisa, Madison (as a writer) and three other people I've loved working with over the years will join me on the Global Digital Strategies team. We are blessed to work under and support our Vice President, Ken Cochrum, who leads the Digital Strategies team.</p>,<p>Together, God-willing, we will do this so that we can even more effectively tell the gospel story <em>so that everyone knows someone who follows Jesus Christ.</em></p>,<p>You are so critical in our being able to do this work.</p>,<a href="https://give.cru.org/0258043" data-role="cta">Be our Gospel Champion</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://brockmans.org/transition/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ae74ea1-47b0-46b7-8e04-a262dece0eaa</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 21:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>